Hey, Trap Stars, checking in to see if we are ready today to let go of Black-Owned as some signifier that it is worthy of support.
Just because Black people own something doesn't mean they do so ethically.
It doesn't mean that the funds go back to the community.
It doesn't mean that they treat their employees or their staff, etc. on a high level.
It doesn't mean literally anything other than it's Black-Owned.
Yeah, and the fact of the matter is, if they're a Black capitalist and their business is ultimately upholding and perpetuating capitalism,
which, for those who don't know, is actively against the advancement of Black folks, then what are we doing?
Because y'all done let this whole Black thing go too far.
It got you voting for people that don't give a damn about you.
It got you spending money in places that don't give a damn about you.
And it got you trusting folks that are absolutely untrustworthy.
So it's almost like you're judging people based on the color of their skin.
It's got to be a better way.